漫威漫画
刚从烤箱里拿出来
Fresh out of the oven.
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
-我帮她吃  -不行
- I'll help her eat this. - All right. No! Hey!
-扎克  我...  -我去拿柠檬
- Zach! I-- - I'll get the lemonade.
-听着  你们能拿几个杯子吗  -我有  给
- Listen, go-- Can we have some cups? - I got some. Here you go.
翻译     小酸奶   一只虾
-四个  没错  -四个
- Four of them. Four. Yeah! - Four?
-要倒了  -太重了  好  准备好了吗
- It's gonna fall. - This is heavy. Okay, okay. Ready?
翻译     我有猫我骄傲
-一  -好了  准备好了
- One. - Okay. Ready?
-这边  谢谢
- Over here. - Thank you.
好了
That's done.
校对     惩罚奶
好了  看起来真棒  这边
It's done! Oh, that looks good. Right there.
看起来真棒
Oh, this looks great!
-给  -谢谢你  先生
- Here you are! Yup. - Oh, thank you, sir.
时间轴    奶粉袋   想念Gallifrey的Wholock
-看起来真不错  -小心
- That looks good. - Be very careful.
的确很棒
It is good.
后期     惩罚者8T
-真是太棒了  -这真是
- Oh, you guys, this is great! - It's sort of...
-好了  -太好了
- All right! - Good! -
总监     惩罚奶
注意了  要敬酒了
Attention! A toast.
欢迎回家  弗兰克
Welcome home, Frank.
-欢迎回家  弗兰克  -欢迎回家  爸爸
- Welcome home! Frank - Welcome home, Dad.
谢谢你们  好了  伙计
Thank you. All right, buddy.
很高兴能来这里
It's good to be here.
爸爸  快看
Oh, boy. Daddy, look!
看看你
Hey, look at you.
天啊
Oh, my God!
这上面有我的名字
This one has my name on it.
-我去拿  行吗  -好
- I'm gonna grab that, all right? - Yeah.
伙计们  等等  等等  等等
Guys, guys, wait up! Wait up, wait, wait.
不  不不不不不
No! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等  等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, just wait!
等等
Just wait!
不
No!
反正我觉得我总有一天会死在这树林里
I always figured I'd die in these woods anyway.
我一定会背你下山
I'm gonna get you off this mountain.
埋葬我  伙计
Bury me, man.
埋葬我  保证你会埋葬我  好吗
Just bury me. Promise me you'll bury me, okay?
待在这里  我会回来的  我会回来的  加纳
You stay here. I'll be back. I'm coming back, Gunner.
待在这里  我会回来的  加纳
You stay here. I'm coming back, Gunner.
弗兰克快死了
Frank's dying.
人人影视字幕组原创翻译
Netflix原创剧集
后期  惩罚者8T
总监  惩罚奶
翻译  小酸奶
翻译  一只虾
翻译  我有猫我骄傲
时间轴  奶粉袋
时间轴  想念Gallifrey的Wholock
校对  惩罚奶
惩罚者
第一季第六集
-血压90/60  -太低了
- Blood pressure's 90 over 60. - That's low.
他需要血吗  我是万能型血
Does he need blood? I'm a universal donor.
血不是问题  他的体温高达40度
Blood's not the problem. His temperature is 104.
他感染了
He's septic.
我一直在给他输液  服抗生素
I've been giving him fluids and antibiotics.
我们得先把箭拔出来
None of that's gonna do any good
不然这样根本没用
until we get that arrow out of him.
外界异物上全是细菌
It's a foreign object filled with bacteria.
身体试图对抗  但是做不到  所以...
The body's trying to fight it but can't, so...
白血球激增  发烧  全身发炎
white blood cells, fever, systemic inflammation...
-好吧  -抗生素只是在做无用功
- Right. - Antibiotics are fighting a losing battle.
那你准备把箭拔出来吗
So you're gonna, uh, pull it out?
如果我直接拔出来
If I pull it straight out,
那造成的伤害会比将箭头穿过去更大
then it's gonna cause more damage than it went in.
-你没事吧  -没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
很好  因为你要帮我按住他
Okay, good. 'Cause you're gonna have to help me hold him still.
嗯  就现在
Yeah, like now, yeah.
好吧  数到三  一  二
Right, on three. One, two... -
二  三
Two. Three.
-我扶住了  -很好
- Okay, I got it. - There you go. Good.
扶住了  压住
Hold that. Keep the pressure on.
只有将箭穿过来
The only way out is through.
上帝啊
Jesus!
清醒点  别吓得尿了  明白了吗
Stay with me. Do not lose your shit. You understand me?
-说一遍  -我不会吓得尿了  我没事
- Say it. Say it! - I will not lose my shit. I'm good.
好了  找到了
Okay. We got it.
找到了
Got it.
-按住这里  压住  -操
- Here, hold this. Keep the pressure on. - Oh, fuck!
你能不能  重新...
Can you just go-- get it again for...
-一  二  三  -好
- One, two... three. - Okay.
-我们好了吗  -嗯
- So we done? - Yup.
-好  -我们现在只要灼烧伤口
- Good. - All we gotta do is cauterize the wound.
操
Fuck.
给
Here.
现在好了吧
Now we done?
想来点咖啡吗
You want some coffee?
你为什么要去找他
Why'd you have to go after him?
汉德森手上有我们需要的信息
Henderson had some information we needed.
我说的是弗兰克
I'm talking about Frank.
你看看他的状态
Look at the state of him.
这都是你的错  伙计
This is all your fault, man.
你觉得你们这样做会有什么用吗
Do you think any of this is gonna make any difference?
听着
Look...
我必须要相信有  我是说...
I have to believe that. I mean...
对你来说是的
Yeah, for you.
但是他呢
But what about him?
天啊  一连两晚
God! Two nights in a row.
这次总不能怪酒劲了
You can't blame the alcohol this time.
我可不会给你钥匙什么的
You're not getting a key or anything.
我知道我应该无视我所看到的东西
So, I know I'm supposed to ignore what I'm looking at here.
界限或者...
Boundaries or...
交往原则之类的  但是...
rules of engagement for whatever this is, but...
这是什么东西  迪娜
What the hell is this, Dinah?
是工作
It's work.
我肯定是个十足的笨蛋
You know... I must be a real idiot...
因为我刚刚才突然想到你可能
because it is only just now occurring to me that you might be...
在利用我
using me.
你有什么没告诉我
What are you not telling me here?
我是一名国安局调查员  比利
I'm a Homeland Security Investigator, Billy.
我有很多没告诉你的
There's a lot I'm not telling you.
你为什么这么想败坏一个死人的名声
Why are you so intent on pissing on the memory of a dead man?
不是这么一回事
That's not what this is.
你还是穿上裤子吧  你看上去很蠢
Why don't you put your pants on? You look kinda stupid right now.
有的人撒谎很厉害  根本不会眨眼
You know, some people are good liars. They don't blink an eye.
其他人就不怎么样  你就很不擅长
Others, not so much. You... you're bad at it.
所以我猜你只是为了逃避才这样刻薄
So I'm guessing that you just get mean in order to avoid doing it.
我没撒谎  我只是没有告诉你一些事
I'm not lying, I'm just not telling you anything.
一些事
About something.
不  一些...关于我朋友弗兰克的事
No, something... something about my friend, Frank.
你知道  他们一直没能找到他的尸体
You know that they never found his body?
你的...
Is that in...
文件里有写吗
in your file?
有
Yeah. It is.
我一直很奇怪
I always wondered about that.
要去上班了
Gotta go to work.
该死
Oh, shit.
加纳
Gunner!
万一他还在那边呢
What if he's still out there?
-弗兰克  -我得...我得去找他
- Hey! Frank. Shh. - I gotta get... I gotta get him.
放松  你得躺下来
Relax. You gotta lay down.
-躺下  -他还在外面
- Lay down. - He's out there.
你得躺下来  听好了
You gotta lay down. Listen.
加纳死了
Gunner's dead.
-我...我丢下了他  -很遗憾
- I did... I left him. - Sorry.
我得回去找他
I gotta go back for him.
-得回去找他  -我都处理好了
- Gotta go back for him. - I took care of it.
-什么意思  什么意思  -我都处理好了
- What do you mean? What do you mean? - I took care of it.
他会有一个体面的葬礼
He's gonna get a proper burial.
好好休息吧
Get some rest.
谢谢
Thank you.
我从来没得到过一句谢谢
I didn't get a thank you.
只有别人的中指
I got the finger.
别人的唾弃
I got spit on.
但是
But...
副总统给我钉了一枚银星奖章
the vice president pinned a silver star on me.
所以你才服役吗  为了他人的感激
Is that why you served? For gratitude?
1968年4月
April, 1968.
三歧往西20英里的地方
About 20 miles west of Tam Ky.
我杀了13个东南亚猴子  用他们的手榴弹
I killed 13 of those gooks with their own grenades.
"英勇行动"
"For gallantry in action."
你们根本不知道你们有多幸福
You guys have no idea how good you got it.
"谢谢你的贡献"
"Thank you for your service."
需要听到"谢谢"的人都是娘娘腔
Anybody who needs a "Thank you" is a goddamn pussy.
我们不需要  你这个可怜的老混蛋
We don't need it, you miserable old bastard.
也许是我们应得的
Maybe we earned it?
你为什么而战斗  奥康纳
Why'd you fight, O'Connor?
那天和那天以后的日子  是什么驱使着你
What drove you that day, and all the days after?
只是做我该做的事
Just doing my duty.
那你为什么这么生气
Then why are you so angry about it?
你做了你自己应该做的事
You did what you were supposed to do, right?
像我们一样
As we all did.
那你为什么要来这里
So why come here?
我觉得这些人需要听听反例
I figure these guys need to hear an alternative.
他们已经有妈妈牵着他们的手了
They already got mommy holding their hand.
爸爸得让他们坚强起来  把他们送回去
Daddy's here to toughen 'em up. Send 'em back out there.
回到现实世界中
Out into the real world.
一个根本不会在意我们的世界
A world that does not give a shit about us.
在前线后  真正的美国人永远排在最后
Where real Americans are put at the back of every goddamn line.
路易斯在哪里  你见到过他吗
Where's Lewis? Have you seen him?
他是个聪明的孩子  他能看到光
He's a bright kid. He saw the light.
他听到真相后心里有数
He knows the truth when he hears it.
他知道光用言语无法赢得这场战争
He knows words aren't gonna win this fight.
没有什么"赢得战争"一说
There is no winning the fight.
我受训做看护兵的时候  他们给了我一头羊
When I trained as a corpsman, they gave me a goat.
我把我的命名为卡修斯  因为他永远是最棒的
I named my goat Cassius, because he was a G.O.A.T., right?
卡修斯是拳王阿里的本命
永远是最棒的缩写为GOAT  同山羊
你知道他们怎么对那头羊的吗
You know what they did to that goat?
他们把它炸飞
They blew him up.
把它切伤
They cut him.
模拟他受到爆炸伤害
Gave him simulated IED injuries.
然后要你去拯救它的性命
And then they tell you to go out there and save his life.
因为我们就是这样学的
Because that's how we learned.
一遍又一遍
Over and over again.
那种日子算什么
What sort of life is that?
你...你经历这一切
You know, you... you go through all this shit
只是为了包扎好准备下一次伤害
just to get patched up and go do it all over again.
如果你待得够久  总会受伤
If you stay in the game long enough, you're gonna get got.
我们和那些羊有什么区别
How are we any different from that goat?
这不是应该由你来告诉我们吗
Aren't you supposed to tell us that?
我完全不知道答案  伙计
I'm all out of answers, man.
后来呢  卡修斯怎么样了
What happened? To Cassius?
它最终还是死了
He died, eventually.
它死于...
He died of, uh...
太多次伤害
of just too much.
你的数学考试怎么样
How was your math test?
算上附加分有105分
105 with the bonus question.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
你知道吗  也许
Well, then, you know what? Maybe...
也许今晚你能好好休息一下
maybe you can take the night off, huh?
你弟弟呢
Where's your brother?
他在外面玩他的滑板
He's outside on his skateboard.
扎克
Zach!
-扎克  -妈妈
- Zach! - Mom!
不  没关系
No, it's all right.
又吃汉堡
Burgers again?
这个滑板是哪里来的
Where'd you get that skateboard?
迪内希的  我借的
From Dinesh. I'm borrowing it.
你当着我的面撒谎
You're lying right to my face.
我知道这个滑板是你偷的
I know that you stole that skateboard.
迪内希的妈妈打电话来了
Dinesh's mother called me.
我本来还不相信  直到我亲眼看到你这样
I didn't believe her until I saw it with my own eyes.
住手  你现在变成一个恶霸了吗
Hey, stop it! Are you a bully now? Is that what this is?
这个家里全是告密者和叛徒
This family's full of snitches and traitors.
要是她今天没出卖我  明天也会说的
If she didn't narc on me today, she'll do it tomorrow.
我们就是这样
That's, like, what we do here!
你名单上的一个人出现了  加纳·汉德森
One of the guys on your list turned up. Gunner Henderson.
-他在哪里  -死了
- Where is he? - Dead.
在肯塔基的一座山上
On a mountain in Kentucky.
关上门
Close the door.
我们要去肯塔基吗
Are we going to Kentucky?
你可以说"有个好消息  有个坏消息  迪娜"
You could've said, "Good news, bad news, Dinah."
-我想是吧  -我找警长
- I guess I could have. - Can I speak to the sheriff?
这里是国安局  事态紧急
This is Homeland Security. It's urgent.
-谢谢  -我们要去肯塔基
- Thanks. - We're going to Kentucky.
谢谢
Thanks.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven, come in.
乌鸦  回复  我是黑鸟
Raven! Blackbird, come in!
哪里来的信号
Where's that coming from?
乌鸦  乌鸦  我是...
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is-- -
回复  乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Come in, Raven. Blackbird.
回复  乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑...
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Black--
-听起来好像是录音  -黑鸟呼叫鲍尔小队
- Sounds like a recording. - Blackbird calling Bower team.
在全频道重复
Repeating across all frequencies.
乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑鸟  黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Blackbird. Blackbird to Raven.
黑鸟呼叫鲍尔小队
Blackbird calling Bower team.
我一直在监听广播频道
I've been monitoring radio chatter.
乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Raven, this is Blackbird.
以防万一听到关于我们或我们目标的情报
Just in case we hear something about us or one of our targets.
一般都不知道是什么  杂音
Mostly it's just been random shit, you know, dead air.
呼叫  乌鸦
Come in, Raven.
-你知道这是什么吗  -嗯
- You know what this is? - Yeah.
我是乌鸦
I'm Raven.
乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Raven, this is Blackbird.
你在吗  弗兰基
You out there, Frankie?
是谁
Who is that?
是比利·罗素  我们一起服过役  他是我朋友
It's Billy Russo. We served together. He's a friend.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦  黑鸟
Blackbird to Raven. Blackbird.
-他...  -黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
- Does, uh... - Blackbird to Raven.
-他知道你还活着吗  -应该不知道
- Does he know you're alive? - Nah. I don't think so.
-呼叫  乌鸦  -听上去好像他知道
- Come in, Raven. - You see, that sounds to me like he does.
弗兰克  我们需要担心吗
Frank... do we need to worry about this?
我刚说了他是我朋友  我没说吗
I just told you he's my friend. Didn't I just say that?
哪种朋友
What kind of friend?
生死之交的那种
The life or death kind. That's what kind.
就这样吗  得了吧
That's all I get? Come on,
弗兰克  现在情况很严重
Frank, this is a serious development here.
好吗  一个我从来没听说过的人
All right? Some guy, I never heard of him,
突然间在全频道广播找你
all of a sudden he's broadcasting your name all over the radio.
-我刚怎么和你说的  -黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
- What did I just say to you? - Blackbird to Raven, come in?
他为什么现在找你
Why is he calling you now?
乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Blackbird.
我不知道
I don't know.
今天真冷
Cold today.
不错  能让人清醒点
That's good. Wakes people up.
女士  加入我们
Ma'am, join with us to
重申你的第二修正案权利吧
reaffirm your God-given Second Amendment rights.
不用了  谢谢
Oh, I'm good, thanks.
每天他们都会失去一点他们的自由
Every day they lose more of their liberty.
正在那幢楼里被慢慢蚕食...
It's being chipped away, in that building, right now...
他们却浑然不知
and they don't even know it.
你们在抗议吗  有许可吗
This a protest? You have a permit?
不  我们没有抗议  我们在分发作品
No, we're not protesting. We are handing out literature
完全免费  也是百分百受法律保护的
which is free, and 100% allowed by law.
有个要受审的人  一个好人  一个老师
There's a guy on trial in there. A good man, a teacher,
带着枪走进教室...
who carried his gun into the classroom-- -
好吧  那你们是在抗议
Okay, so you are protesting.
-有什么事  警官  -你们可以拿着这些回家
- What can we do for you, officer? - You can go home. Take this.
恕我直言  长官  你无权要求我们离开
Respectfully, sir, you have, um, no right to ask us to move.
如果集会或抗议行动用到扩音设备
A permit is required if amplification is involved
才需要申请许可
in any gathering or protest.
没有麦克风  没有扩音器  也就不需要许可
No mic, no speaker, no permit needed.
我们没有车辆  少于20人
We have no vehicles. We're fewer than 20 people.
我们也没有堵塞人行道或大楼入口
We're not blocking the sidewalk or the entrance of a building.
这里是市法院  你们想待在这里吗
This is a city courthouse. You wanna hang out here?
我就是许可  孩子  今天不合适  回去吧
I'm your permit, son. And today is not the day. Go home.
走吧  我们去买一杯咖啡
Come on, let's, uh, get a cup of coffee, huh?
先生  请你注明在整个事件中
Sir, please mark that in this encounter
我没有做任何违反法律的事
I have done absolutely nothing against the law.
我一直保持绝对的尊重
I've been 100% respectful.
然而你却只是编造出你的规矩
What you are doing, however, is making up the rules as you go,
而不是好好执法
not enforcing them.
你的工资是我...是我们付的
I pay your salary... We-- We all pay your salary.
那就做好保护和服务的工作
So protect and serve.
乖乖照我说的做
Just do as I tell you, huh?
-算了吧  -这...
- Just let it go. - Now...
这个国家不是这样运作的
that is not how this country works.
你刚刚是要去拿我的枪吗
Did you just reach for my gun?
不  长官  我没有
No, sir, I did not.
我刚刚看到你要拿我的枪
I just saw you reach for my gun.
我没有  而且我有一个证人
I didn't, and I have a witness.
汉德森手上中了一枪  胸口中了一枪
So Henderson takes a bullet to the hand, one through the chest.
在这里流血过多而死
Bleeds out, right here.
有人专门打电话给当地警察
Someone took the trouble to call the local cops
告诉他们尸体在哪里  有人想让人找到他
and tell them where the body was. Someone wanted him to be found.
有人当时和他一起
Someone was up here with him.
也留了很多血  他们往那边走了
Bleeding hard, too. They went that way.
你怎么想
What are you thinking?
这里发生过激烈的枪战
There was a serious firefight here.
一支武装队伍出现  但是却被打得大败
A well-armed team showed up and got their asses kicked.
我想这就是
I guess that's what happens
去一名特种部队士兵的领地
when you go after a Special Forces soldier
招惹他的后果
on his own turf.
两名
Two.
-我没懂  -加纳和离开的那个人
- I don't follow. - Gunner and whoever walked away.
加纳和他的兄弟杀死了入侵小队
Gunner and his buddy kill the assault team,
但是加纳中枪了
but Gunner's been hit.
所以他的兄弟带他下山
And so his buddy starts taking him down the hill.
但是他们只走到这里  加纳快死了...
But they only get this far. Gunner is dying...
另一个人就想去找人帮忙
so the other guy tries to go and get help.
当地医院没有人中枪伤
No record of anyone turning up at local hospitals
求救的记录
with gunshot wounds.
但他报警是为了让人找到加纳
But then he calls the cops because he wants Gunner to be found.
海军陆战队永远不会丢下任何人
Marines never leave a man behind.
你觉得另一个人是卡塞尔
And you think Castle was the other guy.
将血迹和他的DNA进行比对
Run that blood against his DNA.
-加三倍急  不要声张  -好的
- Triple fast and quiet. - You got it.
交给他们吧  我们调查完了
Let 'em in. We're done here.
你想要哪个  肉汁火鸡还是索尔斯伯利牛肉饼
What do you want, turkey and gravy or Salisbury steak?
火鸡  看看
Turkey. Look at that.
在感恩节  你家...
At Thanksgiving, your house...
你做饭还是你妻子做饭
do you cook or is that your wife?
不  我们家一人做一半
No, we go half and half.
我负责火鸡  莎拉负责配菜
I'm on the turkey. Sarah does all the sides.
填料  烤土豆  特别棒
Stuffing, twice-baked potato. Amazing.
我们总是有很多客人
I mean, we always have a lot of people...
亲戚  朋友之类的
extended family, you know, friends,
我们就是一人做一半  我们...
and we were just, like, 50-50. We make...
我们合作很愉快
We made a good team.
总是玛利亚做饭
Maria always cooked.
都是...都是一些经典菜式
Yeah, it was... You know, it was old-school.
火鸡之类的  但是...
Turkey, all that, but...
但总会有通心粉  肉丸  沙司酱
There was always ziti. Yeah. Meatballs, sauce.
她的祖母来自西西里岛
Her, uh... her grandma came over from Sicily, so she...
她很清楚自己在做什么
she knew what she was doing.
你知道吗...
Yeah, man. You know something...
如果我现在闭上眼睛  我就能...看到她
if I close my eyes right now, I could... I could see her.
我是说
I mean...
我能看到她
like, I see her.
总是很简单的场景  就像...
It's always something simple, you know. Like...
就像站在厨房里  在通电话...
like, standing in the kitchen, talking on the phone and...
然后...
and, uh...
如果还有音乐
if there was ever any music, like,
可能从任何地方飘来的  她会...
it could be coming from anywhere, she'd...
她会跟着舞动
she'd just start moving to it, you know.
老天  她跳舞真好看
Boy, she could dance.
有时她会...  她会发现我在看她
Sometimes she would, uh... She'd catch me looking at her.
老兄  我...
Man, I was...
我完全被迷倒
I was done.
我也不知道  我们...
Yeah. I don't know, we were, uh...
我们不算非常完美  但...
we were far from perfect, but...
当我想起她的时候  好像所有不好的事
when I remember her, it's like all the shitty stuff,
就消散了  就是...
it fades away, you know, it just...
当我想她时  总会想到她的笑容  你知道吗
When I think about her, she's always got that smile, you know?
所以  你的朋友...
So, your friend, uh...
比利
Billy.
-嗯  -他...可不是开玩笑  弗兰克
- Yeah. - He's, uh... he's serious, Frank.
他现在是个...私营军火承包商
He's a... you know, private military contractor now.
负责海外政府的合同  这人...
Connected. Government contracts overseas. This guy is...
我觉得如果他不知道你还活着
I got the impression that this is not a man
绝对不会贸然这样想联系你
that's gonna reach out to you unless he knows that you're alive.
他不知道  可能会怀疑  不过他不知道
No, he doesn't know. He might suspect it, but he doesn't know.
你不准备打给他吗
You're not gonna call him?
我们是海军陆战队  我们能接受失望
We're Marines. We can handle disappointment.
可能有其他人知道你还活着
Maybe somebody else knows that you're alive,
然后利用比利
and they're using Billy--
你要明白
Something you need to understand.
我有过两个家  好吗
I had two families, all right?
我有玛丽亚和孩子们  我还有部队
I had Maria, I had the kids, and I had my unit.
我曾是位父亲丈夫  但我也曾是一名海军陆战队
I was a father and a husband, but I was also a Marine.
我热爱当海军陆战队  我爱死这工作
And I loved being a Marine. I loved that shit.
听着  不管我愿不愿意承认  有些时候
And look, I-- There were times, whether I wanna admit it or not,
比起和我的孩子们一起
but I would've rather been neck deep in blood
我更喜欢上战场
and bullets and shit
和战友们一起出生入死
and be with my unit than with my kids.
这有我得接受这一点  就是这样
That's something I gotta make peace with. That's what that is.
但我和比利·罗素  我们一起服役了八年
But me and Billy Russo, we served together, we did eight years.
我们俩互相照应
He got my back, I got his back.
我不知道  你得承认这也太巧了
I don't know, you gotta admit this is a hell of a coincidence.
比利·罗素是我的家人
Billy Russo is my family.
他是我的家人
He's my family.
进来
Yeah?
你说对了  现场的血是卡塞尔的
You were right. Blood on the scene matches Castle's DNA.
就知道
Knew it.
那好  卡塞尔和加纳在山上
Okay, so, you got Castle and Gunner up there on that mountain,
跟谁对抗
versus who?
不想让坎大哈行动暴露的人
Whoever doesn't want Kandahar to come out.
他们在消灭证据
They're cleaning house.
中情局  军方
CIA, the military.
有人派了暗杀小组到那山上
Someone sent a death squad up that mountain.
该死  要动用的资源...还有这胆量
Shit, the resources to do that... The sheer balls to do that.
如果卡塞尔活了下来
If Castle survived...
他流血不止地从那山上下来
he came off that mountain bleeding like a stuck pig.
没错  我们要找到他
Yeah. We've gotta find him.
如今  该上哪儿找一个已经死了的海军陆战队
Now, where does one find dead Marines these days?
因为在脸书陌陌可都没看到他更新
Because he's not on Facebook or Tinder. I checked.
你为什么要把我保释出来
Why'd you bail me out?
我想如果你不得不打给我
I figured that if you had to call me,
那就是你不想让你爸知道
then you didn't want to call your dad.
那就没有其他人能帮你了
And that meant there was no one else.
-我不想要放弃你  -你想帮我吗
- And I wasn't about to abandon you. - You wanted to help me?
是的没错  路易斯
That's all I want, Lewis.
那你为什么要跟比利·罗素一起来搞我
Then why screw me over with Billy Russo?
路易斯  如果你还意识不到
Lewis, if you can't see going back into a war zone
回到战区是你最不该做的事
is about the worst thing that you can do,
那我没做错什么
then I did the right thing.
-轮不到你说  -所以你觉得我背叛了你
- Not your call. - So what, you think I betrayed you?
你被抓的时候奥康纳在哪
Where... Where was O'Connor when you got arrested?
你有找过他吗
Did you try him?
他没来  对吗
Oh, he didn't come, did he?
我查过他的记录  他并不是你所了解的人
I pulled his records. He's not what you think he is.
你知道他常说的那什么银星勋章吗
And you know that silver star he always talks about?
他说的那个故事
The story that goes with it?
他从来没去过越南
He never served in Vietnam.
他在77年才报的名  他从没经历过战争
He didn't sign up till '77 and never saw a combat.
他是个大骗子  路易斯
He's a fraud and a liar, Lewis.
不像你  他没服过役  他根本不值得你尊重
He didn't serve, not like you. And he's not worth your respect.
所以...你为什么不留下
So... so why don't you stay?
-路易斯  -怎么了  伙计
- Hey, Lewis. - What's going on, man?
你要去哪
Where you going?
这地方真适合来个浪漫的道歉
This is a great place for a romantic apology.
或是杀人  随便了
Or a mob hit. Whichever.
我本来以为找艳遇的话
You know, I figured if I ever got to have a clandestine affair,
会有更多有趣的枕边话
there'd be a lot more intriguing pillow talk
不会在海边吹冷风
and a lot less freezing my balls off on the waterfront.
显然现在也不是邀请我来打和好炮的
And as this is clearly not an invitation to make up sex,
我还是站在这里
I figure I'm just gonna stand here
等你告诉我你想要什么吧
and wait while you tell me what you want.
因为你有事相求  对吗
'Cause you do want something, right?
我想你跟我说说弗兰克·卡塞尔
I want you to tell me about Frank Castle.
为何你不跟我说说你知道他些什么
Why don't you tell me what you know about Frank Castle?
卡塞尔还活着
Castle's alive.
你可能已经知道了  也可能还被蒙在鼓里
Maybe you already knew that, maybe not.
我现在告诉你  我知道了这事
I'm telling you I know it.
我有说错吗
Am I lying?
我觉得没有
No, I don't think you are.
你不知道吗
You didn't know?
我觉得就算你知道
You strike me as a guy who would have protected him
你也会护着他
even if you did.
如果你在撒谎的话  那你肯定很擅长说谎
Well, if you're a liar, you're one of the good ones.
-为什么要跟我说这事  -我要把卡塞尔抓回来
- Why are you telling me this now? - I need to bring Castle in.
如果你已经知道他在哪  我需要你帮忙
If you already knew where he was, I was gonna ask for your help.
如果有人能找到他  大概就是你了
As it is, if there's anyone who can find him, it's probably you.
-你能找到他吗  -为什么我可以
- Can you? - Why would I?
我想他查清楚了我的坎大哈案件
I think he knows everything about my Kandahar case.
嗯  那对他有什么好处
Okay. So how does that help him?
因为我觉得他在自己查这件事
Because I think he went after it himself.
有人把他在山上打得半死
And somebody left him half dead on a mountain.
我猜他受了伤  他需要帮助
I think he's hurt, and he needs help.
他对付的那些人...
The people he's up against...
他会死的  比利
He's gonna get himself killed, Billy.
我们都不想他死  不是吗
Neither of us want that, right?
没错
All right.
我会去碰碰运气
I'll shake the tree and see what falls out.
话说  我挺喜欢这样的
I like this, by the way.
我喜欢你信任我
I like that you trusted me with this.
我还是不会给你钥匙的
You're still not getting a key.
你好啊  社工
Hey, social worker...
我患了社会病
I got a social disease.
要来点抗生素吗
You want some penicillin for that?
-最近如何  见到你真好  -怎么样  伙计
- How you doing? Good to see ya. - What's up, man?
-你见过弗兰克吗  -什么
- You seen Frank? - What?
弗兰克·卡塞尔
You know... Frank Castle.
我们的朋友  死了的那个
Our friend. Our dead friend.
你最近见过他吗
You seen him recently?
我不清楚你在说什么  比利
I-- I'm gonna need some help with this, Billy.
你什么意思  问我有没有去过墓地
What do you mean? Have I been back to the cemetery?
我有没有看见鬼魂或是闪回
Am I seeing ghosts or having flashbacks?
你在说什么
What are we talking about?
弗兰克还活着  伙计
Frank's alive, man.
抱歉  我得看看你是不是知道
Sorry, I had to find out if you knew.
你为什么觉得我知道
And why do you think that?
我不能告诉你我是怎么知道的  但是
I can't tell you how I found out, but...
我确实知道了  而且现在我得找到他
I found out, and now I gotta find him.
当然  我一直希望
Of course, I was hoping
你从始至终都在骗我
that you were lying to me this whole time.
如果是这样  至少我知道从何查起了
If you were, at least I'd have a lead on where to start.
我一直在无线电中转播以前军队的联络暗号
I'v been putting out the old unit call on the radio.
他有回应吗
Has he answered?
好了  我  我会告诉你
All right, I'm... I'm gonna tell you,
但是得保密  行吗
but on the down-low, all right?
我知道是因为一些政府的人知道了
I found out because some government people know,
而且他们觉得或许我也知道
and they thought that maybe I knew, too.
他们还说弗兰克现在伤得很重
They also said that Frank is hurt pretty bad right now.
所以
So...
如果你能为我提供一些线索的话
if you've got any idea where I should start...
所以  你要怎么做  你要帮他们吗
So, you're... What? You're gonna help them?
我要帮弗兰克
I'm gonna help Frank.
我可以帮他离开这里  伙计  清白自由地出去
I could get him out of here, man. Free and clear.
我辜负了他一次
I failed him once before.
现在我有机会弥补
Now is my chance to make things right.
我又为你撒了谎
I lied for you again.
你做得对  科特
You did the right thing, Curt.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven, come in.
整点播放  这家伙真有决心
Every hour on the hour. This guy's determined.
请回复  乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Blackbird.
他说他想帮你  他说他能帮你
He said he wanted to help you. That he could help you.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven.
不管他提供什么帮助  要我说  你应该接受
Whatever he's offering, if you ask me, you should take it.
越少人知道我活着  他们越安全
Less people know I'm alive, safer it is for them.
但是你呢  你现在可不安全
But what about you? You don't look too safe.
你差点没命了 这点你最清楚
You look like a guy that nearly got his ass killed, and you know it.
为了什么呢
And for what? Huh?
乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Raven, this is Blackbird.
-要我说  -你没资格说话
- If I could just add something-- - You don't get an opinion.
在这件事上你没资格
Not in this conversation.
请回复  乌鸦
Come in, Raven.
所以现在怎么办  我继续为你撒谎吗
So, what? I just keep lying for you?
科特  你得去做你认为正确的事
Look, Curt, you... you gotta do what you think is right.
我不会对你有别的要求
I'd never ask you to do anything else.
请回复  乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Blackbird.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦  黑鸟呼叫鲍尔小队
Blackbird to Raven. Blackbird calling Bower team.
别跟任何人提起这个地方  科迪斯
Don't mention this place to anybody, okay, Curtis?
-天哪  你认真的吗  -你得保密
- Jesus Christ. Really? - Please, just keep it to yourself.
乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Raven, this is Blackbird.
你的朋友真是厉害
You got some friends.
乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Raven, this is Blackbird.
你在吗  弗兰克
You out there, Frankie?
乌鸦  我是黑鸟  你在吗  弗兰克
Raven, this is Blackbird. You out there, Frankie?
你相信这个人吗
You trust this guy?
是  是的  我相信
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦  请回复  请回复  乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven. Come in. Come in, Raven.
那么你应该跟他谈谈
Then you should talk to him.
请回复  乌鸦  乌鸦  我是黑鸟
Come in, Raven. Raven, this is Blackbird.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven.
黑鸟呼叫乌鸦  黑鸟呼叫乌鸦
Blackbird to Raven. Blackbird to Raven.
你可能会用到这些螺丝钉
You probably wanna use one of those swing heads.
然后我们继续深入
And we're gonna go after it.
我用个大个的
I'm using a Pit Boss.
泰德  他在用动力蜗杆  看起来不错
Ted, he's using a power worm, and it's very natural looking.
我们用这些卡罗莱纳产的装备
We are using these Carolina rigs--
监狱怎么样  孩子
How was the pokey, kid?
找了个新男友吗
Got yourself a new boyfriend?
你肯定想来杯啤酒
Bet you want a beer.
有些事永远不变  就像纽约警局一样
Some things never change, like the state of the NYPD.
我可以跟你讲些故事
I can tell you some stories.
当初他们唾弃我们  当我们
They spit on us when we came back from--
是  当你们从德克萨斯回来的时候
Yeah, when you came back from Texas.
我看了你的服役档案
Because I read your army records.
你  你从没去过越南
You... you never went to Vietnam.
你有我的档案
You have my records?
你从哪里看到我的档案的  在网上吗
Where'd you get my records from? The Internet?
犹太人管着网络
You know, the Jews run the Internet.
三岐外的空军基地叫什么
What's the name of the air base outside of Tam Ky?
你可以上网搜  但如果你当时在那  你就知道
Well, you could google it. But if you were there, you would know.
是茱莱
It's Chu Lai.
-茱莱空军基地  -茱莱
- Chu Lai Air Base. - Chu Lai.
我怎么可能记得住  我是个老头子
How the hell am I supposed to remember that? I'm an old man.
如果你不喜欢我的故事
Look, if... if you don't like my stories--
不  它们不仅仅是故事
No, they're not just stories!
你不能那么做
You can't just do that.
-滚出我的房子  -你这个骗子
- Get the hell out of my house. - You goddamn liar.
看看这是谁
Look who it is.
起死回生
Back from the dead.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你好  比尔
Hey, Bill.
要来杯啤酒吗
You want a beer?
当然
Hells yeah.
你看上去糟透了
You look like shit.
不是每个人都能像你一样体面的  比尔
Can't all be as pretty as you, Bill.
你怎么一直不联系我
How come you never reached out?
越少人知道我活着
You know, the less people knew I was alive,
对他们越好
the better it is for them.
这些人中有一个在国土安全局工作
Yeah, well, one of them works for Homeland Security.
你知道的吧
You know that, right?
马达尼  你怎么认识她的
Madani, huh? How do you know her?
我的公司  砧板  我现在有个公司
My company, Anvil. I got a company now.
我听说了  很厉害  比尔
I heard. It's... It's very impressive, Bill.
你肯定很喜欢穿高档西装吧
Bet you like to wear fancy suits, don't you?
-是啊  我喜欢  -是啊  你喜欢
- Yes, I do. - Yeah, you do.
不管怎样  我们为他们做一些合同方面的工作
Anyway, we did some contracting work for them.
训练
Training.
我们聊了聊  她向我问起过你
We got to talking. She questioned me about you
因为我们一起服役
because of our service together.
那你和她...你们俩聊过了
So you and her, you... you guys got to talking, huh?
-是的  -我想也是
- Yes, we did. - Yeah. I bet you did.
-你从来没变过  -算你走运  的确没变过
- You never change, huh? - Lucky for you I don't.
虽然我看过她裸体  但是她一心只想找你
I might've seen her naked but she is hot for you, my man.
这个女人可不好对付
That is not a woman you wanna take lightly.
-我有这个感觉  -得了吧
- Yeah, I got that impression. - Come on.
告诉我她不肯说的话
Tell me what she won't.
比尔  我们...
Look, Bill, what we...
我们当初...在地狱犬做的事...
What we were doing... with Cerberus, it was...
比你想的要糟糕得多
It was worse than you thought.
是那个该死的中情局橘色特工
It was that snake, prick CIA Agent Orange.
是他  斯库诺弗
It was him, Schoonover...
你记得那个
You remember that douchebag
停尸房的班内特上校
from mortuary services, Colonel Bennett?
那个又矮又秃的混蛋  你记得他吗
Little bald asshole, you remember him?
这三个人一起在坎大哈贩卖毒品
The three of them were selling heroin out of Kandahar.
他们把死亡的美国士兵开膛
They were opening up US KIAs,
填上毒品  送回家
stuffing it inside, and sending it home.
什么
What?
加纳·汉德森  是他发现的
Gunner Henderson, he found out.
他想揭露这件事
Tried to blow the whistle on the whole thing.
-加纳是个好人  -他死了
- Well, Gunner's a good man. - He's dead.
因此而死
Killed him for it.
该死
Shit.
所以呢  你准备自己一个人扳倒他们吗
So... what? You're just gonna take them all on yourself?
目前进展如何
How's that going for you so far?
为什么不交给国安局处理呢
Why don't you just let Homeland do it, man?
马达尼  她和你一样很想把他们抓起来
Madani, she... she wants them just as bad as you do.
不
No.
你真的觉得玛丽亚会希望你这样做吗
You really think this is what Maria would've wanted for you?
当初我们别无选择
We didn't have a choice back then.
现在我们可以选
Now we do.
什么选择  比尔
What choice is that, Bill?
我可以给你新的护照  社会身份
I could get you a new passport. Social.
新的身份
New identity.
可以让你离开这个国家
Could get you out the country.
让你去国外  做你最擅长的事
Put you overseas, doing what you do best.
和我一起工作吧
Come work with me.
-要给我也穿光鲜西装吗  -你想怎么打扮就怎么打扮
- Gonna put me in a fancy suit? - You could wear whatever you like.
让我送你出城吧  弗兰基
Let me get you out the city, Frankie.
我今晚就可以把你送上船
I could have you on a boat tonight.
你的家人都去世了  但你还是我兄弟
Your family is gone, but you're still my brother.
我了解你
And I know you.
我罩着你
I got you.
你迟到了  其实你迟了好几天
Hey, you're late. You're actually a couple days late.
晚餐几小时前吃完了  没有邀请你
Um, dinner was hours ago, and you weren't even invited.
我知道  我理解你为什么生气
I get it. I understand why you're pissed.
我能进来解释一下吗
You think maybe I could just come in and explain?
我...我很抱歉  你知道...
Yeah, I'm... I'm very sorry, you know...
对不起我没有来吃晚饭
that I didn't make dinner.
我说我会来的  结果我没来  我不是这样的人
I said I was gonna be here and I wasn't. That's not like me.
我不知道你是怎样的人  彼得
I don't know what is like you, Pete.
好吧
Fair enough.
我出了点意外  所以我才没来
I had an accident. That's why I couldn't make it.
你好像经常出意外
Wow, you seem to have a lot of accidents.
是啊
Yeah.
不管怎么样  我没事
Anyway, I'm up. So, it's fine.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯
Yeah, yeah.
最近...事情有点多
Things have... It's been a little much.
我理解
Yeah, I understand that.
-孩子都睡了  -是的  很迟了
- Kids asleep? - Yeah. Yeah, it's late.
然而我却在这里
And yet, here I am...
让你进了我家  你还打扮成这样
letting you into my home. Looking like that.
你真的得多加小心
Yeah, you really ought to be more careful.
我信任你
I trust you.
我不知道为什么  我...很奇怪吧
I don't know why. I... It's funny how that works, huh?
我很高兴你能信任我
I'm glad you do.
-要来杯红酒吗  -不用了
- Do you want a glass of wine? - Uh, no. I'm all good.
-你确定吗  真的吗  -嗯
- You sure? Really? - Yeah. Yeah.
-我要来一杯  -好吧
- I'm gonna have one. - Okay.
再来一杯
Another one.
你...
You, um...
-我能坐下吗  -好
- mind if I sit? - Sure.
我们两个
Well, here we are.
怎么说的来着  痛苦的一对
What is it they say? Misery loves company?
今天很不顺吗
Rough day, huh?
这一周都很不顺
Rough week.
非常非常特殊的一周
Special, special week.
我的儿子突然变成了恶霸
My boy is a bully, all of a sudden.
他打了他的姐姐
He hit his sister.
而我女儿如果拿不到A就会揍自己
And she beats herself up if she gets anything less than an A.
她太想掌控一切了
I mean, she's just so desperate to control everything.
我感觉  我感觉我好像
And I feel like... I feel like I'm living
和两个受伤的人
with these two people...
住在一起
who are hurting...
我不知道该怎么让他们不再受伤
and I don't know how to stop that hurt.
我感觉
And I feel...
我感觉我们好像都在默默流血  你明白吗
I feel like we're all just bleeding out, you know what I mean?
这些孩子  他们...
You know, those kids, they, uh...
我这么说  你可能会很想
You're probably gonna wanna punch me in the mouth
揍我  但是...
for saying this, but...
一切都会好起来的
things are gonna get better for you.
你的一切都好起来了吗
Have they gotten better for you?
我  听着  我孤身一人
For me? Yeah. Yeah, look, I'm alone.
我孤身一人很久了  我...我很喜欢
I've been alone so long, I... I like it.
我藏在其中
You know, I hide in it.
我只知道  走出来的唯一办法
One thing I know is that the only way out...
就是找到你在乎的东西
is to find something that you care about.
这些孩子可能让你气得发疯  他们可能...
Those kids, they might drive you crazy. They might...
可能让你非常生气  但是...
They might make you completely batshit, but...
正因为有他们  你才能熬下来
they're the reason you're gonna get through this.
你找到你所在乎的东西了吗
Have you found something to do that for you?
也许吧
Maybe.
Yeah, maybe.
我觉得利伯曼一家会
I think things are gonna get a lot better
好起来的
for the Lieberman family.
我觉得他们很快就会好起来的
I think they're gonna get a lot better very soon.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
只是感觉
Just a feeling.
希望你说的没错
I hope you're right.
他不会来了
He ain't coming.